Zeitgeist: Addendum is a documentary, history,
war film directed by Peter Joseph.
Zeitgeist: Addendum premiered at the 5th Annual Artivist Film Festival.
Director Peter Joseph stated: "The failure of our world to resolve the issues of war, poverty, and
corruption, rests within a gross ignorance about what guides human behavior to begin with.
It address the true source of the instability in our society, while
offering the only fundamental, long-term solution."
Self, played by Jacque Fresco.
Self, played by Roxanne Meadows.
Self, played by John Perkins.
Self (voice) (archive footage), played by George Carlin.
Self (archive footage), played by Jiddu Krishnamurti.
Self (archive footage), played by Ron Paul.
Zeitgeist is a series of three documentary films released between 2007 and 2011 that present a number
of conspiracy theories, as well as proposals for broad social and economic changes.
The films, Zeitgeist: The Movie (2007), Zeitgeist: Addendum (2008) and
Zeitgeist: Moving Forward (2011) are all directed by Peter Joseph.
The film explores themes of corruption, war on terror,
economic theory, banking, president.
The tone is lighthearted.